ELICITRON

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER AND WEBMASTER

CONTACT

■ ebcitron@gmail.com • elicitron.com • 1(224)307-0844 • Chicago Illinois in elicitron/ • ebcitron

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with the passion and cognitive aptitude to dissect and analyze yesterday's tech to structure and innovate the solutions of tomorrow. Started a business at a young age, managing both Tech and Sales, purchasing broken and used electronics, to tinker, modify, and repair to resell for serious profit. This experience of success in hardware and finance, forged by trial and error manifested a new mentality of limitless personal capability and newfound determination. This led to the realization that software is as fascinating and manipulable as hardware, leading to a deep passion for manipulating electrons to better humanity.

SKILLS

ASSORTED FRONT END **BACK END** HTML5 Python Node.js CSS Scripting Express.js Linux Javascript(ES5/ES6) lava Bash React.js Spring Git Node.js SQL Deployment Redux Firebase Algorithm Analysis Sass/Less MySQL Test Driven Development **React Native** SQLite3 RESTful API postgreSQL

PROJECTS

Brew Plans

Fall 2019 to Current

- Along with team of 5 developers and designers, designed the product from the ground up in a Product Canvas
- Utilized React Native to develop for mobile devices
- · Participated in full SCRUM agile development environment

SpoofMail

Summer 2019 to Current

- Designed out a web app to aid users in their never-ending quest for anonymity
- Collaborated with 5 other Front and Backend developers to build React App
- Designed Backend API with Node.js to use the underlying logic behind the work of our Data Scientist

EDUCATION

Lambda School · Jan. 2019 to Current

Full Stack Web Development Computer Science 2020

Lambda School is a 9+ month accelerated program with an immersive (full-time, 40+ hours/week) hands-on curriculum with a focus on computer science, software engineering, and web development.

Kelley School of Business · Aug. 2014 to May 2016 Accounting and Finance

EMPLOYMENT

CyberSpace MarketPlace

Owner, Engineer, and Salesman 2009 to 2014, 2009 to 2014

- Purchased broken and used electronics for modification and repair
- Cracked open hardware to analyze inner workings and debug by testing electrical components for issues and making subsequent repairs
- Sold unique modifications on common devices such as hacked gaming controllers, installing custom firmware, and aftermarket hardware mods
- Marketed unique colored iPhone housing to peers who desire individuality in a world often uncomfortably uniform

Germ Free Travel

Remote

Webmaster · Apr. 2020 to Current

- In charge of designing, building, and maintaining Germ Free Travel's web-store
- Building an online presence enhancing their brand
- · Optimizing search results and traffic with SEO tools

Lambda School

Remote

Team Lead · Sept. 2019 to Dec. 2019

- Managed a team of 8 students as they worked on Javascript and React projects
- Tasked with guiding and tutoring each student, ensuring they had everything necessary to succeed
- Held daily standup meetings to review the teams progress and answer any questions they had
- Reviewed their GitHub repositories and left significant beneficial comments and suggestions
- Met with each student individually to go over their progress and understanding of the material, further tutoring them when necessary